- ♪ ♪
- This heat wave is brutal.
这热浪太残酷了。
It is way too hot outside.
外面热得要命。
- I call fridge. - I call freezer!
- 我选冰箱。- 我选冷冻室！
- I call my frozen underwear.
- 我选我的冷冻内衣裤。
And all of you thought I was stupid
你们都以为我把它放进去时很傻。
when I put it in there.
啊！内衣冻住了！
Ah! Underwear freeze!
哎哟，哎哟。哦。
Ow, ow. Oh.
好吧，如果我们在春天就这么难受，
- Okay, if we are this miserable in the spring,
想象一下夏天我们会多难受。
imagine how miserable we're gonna be in the summer.
想象一下夏天我们会多么悲惨。
- Actually, I've been thinking about that.
- 实际上，我一直在考虑这个问题。
If we save all of our allowances, birthday money,
如果我们把所有的零花钱、生日钱
and couch coins, we'll have just enough
和沙发硬币都存起来，我们刚好
to get an above-ground pool.
能买一个地上游泳池。
- I'm in. - Me too.
- 我加入。
- I'm out. - What? Why?
- 我也是。
- The smart thing for us to do is buy fur coats.
- 我不参与。
- Wh--
- 什么？为什么？
- Who buys hot fur coats in the summer?
- 对我们来说明智的做法是买毛皮大衣。
- Nobody. That's why they're cheap.
- 没人买。所以它们便宜。
Who buys pools in the summer?
夏天谁买泳池？
- Everybody. That's when you need them.
- 每个人。那是你需要它们的时候。
- Well, that's when they're expensive.
- 嗯，那也是它们贵的时候。
If you guys wanted a pool,
如果你们想要一个泳池，
we should have been talking about this at Christmas.
我们应该在圣诞节就讨论这个。
But summer's coming. This is prime fur coat time.
但夏天快到了。现在是买皮草的最佳时机。
- Okay, we're not doing that, right?
- 好吧，我们不会那么做的，对吧？
- Absolutely not. - No way.
- 绝对不会。 - 不可能。
- Well, good luck getting a pool without my share of the money.
- 那么，没有我的那份钱，祝你们好运买到泳池。
- Dude, a pool makes way more sense
- 哥们，建个游泳池更有意义
than ridiculous fur coats.
比那些荒谬的皮草大衣强多了。
- They're not ridiculous.
- 它们并不荒谬。
How come you guys never care about what I think?
为什么你们从来不在乎我的想法？
- We care.
- 我们在乎。
In fact, we're very concerned
事实上，我们对你的大部分话都很关心
about most of the things you say.
关于你说的很多事情。
- Okay.
- 好吧。
You know what? You convinced me.
你知道吗？你说服我了。
all: Yes!
所有人: 太好了！
- I'm buying my coat. all: What?
- 我要买我的外套。大家: 什么?
- Yup, one with genuine fake fur
- 是的，一件带有真正假毛的外套
that goes from my chin
从我的下巴
all the way down to my ankles.
一直延伸到我的脚踝。
And around my sides and completely up my back.
并且环绕我的两侧，完全覆盖我的背部。
And my arms will be covered in--
我的手臂也将被覆盖——
- We get it. It's a coat.
- 我们明白了。这是一件外套。
- Maybe a fur coat isn't the worst idea.
- 也许一件毛皮外套并不是最糟糕的主意。
- Yes, it is. It is literally the worst idea.
- 不，它实际上是最糟糕的主意。
- Let's go in there and talk some sense into him.
- 我们进去跟他讲讲道理。
What's going on?
发生什么事了？
[dramatic music]
[戏剧性音乐]
♪ ♪
- How did all these piles get here?
- 这些堆是怎么来的？
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
all: Whoa.
哇。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪♪
- Um, Dicky?
呃，迪基？
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
- I'm piling things.
我在堆东西。
- Okay, follow-up question.
好吧，后续问题。
Why are you piling things?
你为什么要堆东西？
- Whenever you guys don't listen to me,
每当你们不听我的话时，
I pile things,
我就堆东西，
and it makes me not want to push you to the ground.
这让我不想把你们推到地上。
- So, uh...
- 那么，呃...
you want to push us the ground?
- 你想把我们推倒在地上？
- Yeah, whenever I'm not piling things.
- 是的，只要我不是在堆东西的时候。
- Pile away.
- 继续堆吧。
- How long has this been going on?
- 这种情况持续多久了？
- Hmm, let me think.
- 嗯，让我想想。
[harp music]
[竖琴音乐]
- I think we should all have greatfruit.
- 我觉得我们都应该吃些greatfruit。
- First of all, it's grapefruit, grape.
- 首先，那是grapefruit，葡萄柚。
- And we're not doing that, right?
- 我们不会那么做的，对吧？
- Absolutely not.
绝对不行。
- No way.
不可能。
- [groans]
[呻吟]
[sighs happily]
[幸福地叹气]
And you still won't let me call it "greatfruit."
你还是不让我叫它“greatfruit”。
- Because its name is still "grapefruit."
因为它的名字仍然是“grapefruit”。
- But there's no grapes in it!
但里面没有葡萄！
And it's a great big fruit.
而且它是一个很大的水果。
- Okay, can we just drop this and go get our pool?
好吧，我们能不能别讨论这个了，去拿我们的泳池？
- No.
不行。
- Well, what if we let you call it "greatfruit?"
好吧，如果我们让你把它叫做“大果”呢？
- It's not about the fruit.
问题不在于水果。
It's about you guys not respecting my ideas.
问题在于你们不尊重我的想法。
You never listen to me,
你们从不听我的，
and you only care about what I think
只有在对你有利的时候，
when it benefits you.
你们才会在乎我的想法。
- That is so not true.
这完全不是真的。
[quietly] Nothing he ever thinks benefits us.
[小声]他从来没想过对我们有利的事。
all: Whoa.
哇。
- I never knew he felt this way.
我从不知道他有这种感觉。
- I do.
我也是。
- I can't believe we annoyed Dicky so much
真不敢相信我们把迪基惹得这么恼火。
that he secretly piles.
以至于他暗地里堆东西。
- I can't believe Dicky would rather have a fur coat
真不敢相信迪基宁愿要一件毛皮大衣。
than a swimming pool.
也不愿意要一个游泳池。
- [sighs] I can't believe
唉，真不敢相信。
Dicky's frozen underwear idea worked.
迪基的冷冻内裤主意居然奏效了。
[laughs]
（笑）
I'm wearing a pair too.
我也穿了一双。
Whoo!
喔！
- I found a way for us to get our pool:
我找到了一个让我们得到泳池的方法：
competitive sport stacking.
竞技叠杯。
There's money to be made here.
这里有赚钱的机会。
Watch this.
看这个。
[crowd cheering]
[人群欢呼]
[whistle blows]
[哨声响起]
- [scoffs] Dicky piles faster than that.
Dicky叠得比这快多了。
- Exactly.
没错。
With Dicky on our team,
有Dicky加入我们队，
we could win one of these tournaments
我们就能赢得其中一个比赛
and have enough money for our pool.
并且有足够的钱来修我们的泳池。
- Well, we can't just ask him to stack for money.
我们不能就这样让他为了钱堆花盆。
I mean, he already thinks
我是说，他可能已经觉得
we only listen to him when it benefits us.
我们只有在对他有利的时候才听他的。
- But this benefits him too.
但这对他也有好处。
He can get that ridiculous summer fur coat.
他可以得到那件荒谬的夏季皮毛大衣。
- Hold on. Sure, he can stack flowerpots,
等等。没错，他可以堆花盆，
but how do we know if he can stack cups?
但我们怎么知道他能不能堆杯子？
- There's only one way to find out.
只有一种方法可以找出答案。
- Ask him? - Trick him.
问他？ - 骗他。
- Works for me.
- 对我来说没问题。
- Who made this? - I did.
- 这是谁做的？
- Well, it's garbage.
- 我做的。
- What does it matter? It's a fake stand.
- 好吧，这是垃圾。
It's only to see if Dicky can stack cups.
- 这有什么关系？这只是个假摊位。
- That is no excuse for this swill.
- 这只是为了看看迪基能不能叠杯子。
I'm in charge now.
- 这不能成为这种劣质品的借口。
- What?
- 我现在负责。
- So, Dicky, we were just wondering
- 什么？
if you would like to help us with...
- 那么，迪基，我们只是想知道你是否愿意帮我们...
this.
这个。
- Our old lemonade stand?
我们的旧柠檬水摊？
Aren't we a little too big for this now?
我们现在不是有点太大了吗？
- Well, don't think of it as our old lemonade stand.
嗯，不要把它想成是我们旧的柠檬水摊。
Think of it as a vintage pop-up juicery
把它想成是一个专门经营手工采摘的
that specializes in hand-harvested
从树上到杯中的工匠级柠檬水。
tree-to-glass artisanal lemon water.
那为什么招牌上写着“柠檬水”？
- Then why does the sign say "Lemonade?"
这是讽刺的。
- It's ironic.
嗯，不管它是什么，我都不会买的。
- Well, whatever it is, I'm not buying it.
没人会买。这就是问题所在。
- Nobody is.
没有人会买。
That's the problem.
这就是问题所在。
So we could really use your opinion
所以我们真的很需要你的意见
on how to stack our cups in an eye-catching way.
关于如何以吸引眼球的方式叠放我们的杯子。
- Oh. You mean like this?
哦，你是说像这样？
- Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
But can you quickly unstack them?
但是你能快速地把它们拆开吗？
- Okay, okay, but can you stack them
好吧，好吧，但是你能把它们叠起来
and then immediately unstack them?
然后立刻拆开吗？
- Why?
为什么？
- Why not?
为什么不？
- I'll do it.
我会做的。
- Yes! - That was so fast.
是的！ - 那太快了。
- What are you guys talking about?
你们在说什么？
- Have you ever considered stacking competitively?
你有没有考虑过参加堆叠比赛？
You know, for money?
你知道，为了钱？
- Oh, well, I've considered money,
哦，好吧，我考虑过钱，
and I have considered stacking
我也考虑过堆叠
but never together.
但从未同时考虑过。
Huh.
嗯。
Nope, not for me.
- Come on, Dicky. We could form a team.
- Yeah, the four of us.
- Why? - Why not?
- I'll do it.
- Hey, Dicky.
How's the lemonade?
- Ironic.
- Can we get two lemonades, please?
- Not here.
Here, you will have hand-harvested
这里，你将品尝到手工采摘的
tree-to-glass artisanal lemon water.
从树上直接到杯中的手工艺柠檬水。
- Hipsters.
- 潮人。
♪ ♪
- Wow, who knew sport stacking was so popular?
- 哇，谁知道叠杯运动这么受欢迎？
[chuckles]
[轻笑]
But some of these parents take this way too seriously.
但有些家长对此太过认真了。
- I checked out the competition, Tom,
- 我查看了比赛，汤姆，
and I think we have a real chance here.
我觉得我们真的有机会。
Call it fair, zebra!
叫它公平，斑马！
- [laughs] Okay, hon.
- [笑] 好吧，亲爱的。
Reel it in. That's Reverend Ames.
冷静点。那是艾姆斯牧师。
Okay. Good luck, kids.
好的。孩子们，祝你们好运。
- We don't need luck. We've got Dicky.
- 我们不需要运气。我们有迪基。
- And jerseys. Check these out.
- 还有球衣。看看这些。
- "The Stackity Doo-Dahs"?
- “斯塔克蒂杜杜达斯”？
- Hey, I make the jerseys. I choose the name.
- 嘿，球衣是我做的。名字也是我选的。
- I would have gladly made the jerseys.
- 我本来很乐意做球衣的。
♪ ♪
- Okay, this is a relay race.
- 好的，这是一场接力赛。
First team to finish stacking wins.
最先完成堆叠的队伍获胜。
On your marks.
各就各位。
Get set.
预备。
Stack.
堆叠。
Yes!
好！
[whistle blows] - Stackity Doo-Dahs move on.
（哨声响起）- Stackity Doo-Dahs晋级。
- Yes!
好！
♪ ♪
- Yes!
好！
♪ ♪
- Moving on. - Yes!
- 继续前进。 - 是的！
♪ ♪
- Stackity Doo-Dahs win,
- Stackity Doo-Dahs赢了，
and they are tournament champion.
他们是锦标赛的冠军。
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- Stackity Doo-Dahs!
- Stackity Doo-Dahs！
In your faces, Count Stackulas.
在你们脸上，Count Stackulas。
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
哇哈哈！
Yes, yes, yes! Whoo!
是的，是的，是的！哇！
- Yes, it's exciting. Sorry, her hat's a little tight.
- 是的，这很激动人心。抱歉，她的帽子有点紧。
- Congratulations.
恭喜。
Here is your trophy and your prize money.
这是你的奖杯和奖金。
See you all on Sunday?
周日见大家？
all: Yes, Reverend.
是的，牧师。
- We're getting our pool. The plan worked.
我们要建游泳池了。计划成功了。
- Wh--what plan?
什么计划？
- Plan? - Pssssh!
计划？
- What plan? - Wait a minute.
什么计划？
You guys were just using me to get your pool.
等等。你们只是利用我来建游泳池。
- No, it's not just our pool.
不，不只是我们的游泳池。
It'll be yours too.
它也会是你的。
- But I don't want a pool.
但我并不想要一个游泳池。
This is what I'm talking about.
我说的就是这个。
You guys never listen to me.
你们从来不听我的。
Well, maybe you'll hear this.
好吧，也许你会听到这个。
- Wait. No, you can't do that.
等等。不，你不能那样做。
We all won that money.
我们所有人都赢得了那笔钱。
- "We"? I did all the work.
“我们”？我做了所有的工作。
But don't worry-- you can still earn your pool
但别担心——你仍然可以通过你的小柠檬水摊赚到你的游泳池。
with your little lemonade stand.
那是一个专门经营手工采摘的复古弹出式果汁店。
- It is a vintage pop-up juicery
- 这是一家复古风格的快闪果汁店
that specializes in hand-harvested
专门提供手工采摘的
tree-to-glass artisanal lemon water!
从树上到杯中的工艺柠檬水！
- [sighs] Hipsters.
- [叹气] 潮人。
♪ ♪
- ♪ La-la-la-la-la, la, la, la-la, la, la ♪
- ♪ 啦-啦-啦-啦-啦, 啦, 啦, 啦-啦, 啦, 啦 ♪
- Here's a sentence I never thought I'd say.
- 这句话我从未想过会说。
Two artisanal lemon waters, please.
请给我两杯工艺柠檬水。
- I can't believe Dicky took away all your prize money.
- 我真不敢相信迪基拿走了你所有的奖金。
- It's okay. We're just gonna have to make our pool money
- 没关系。我们只能用传统的方式赚取我们的奖金
the old-fashioned way:
老式的方法：
with a hard day's work.
通过辛勤的工作。
- That'll be $16.
- 总共16美元。
- [spits]
- [吐口水]
- That was $4 you just spit on the ground.
- 你刚刚吐在地上的那口价值4美元。
- We get free refills, right?
- 我们可以免费续杯，对吧？
- Next!
- 下一位！
- $8 for a lemonade?
- 一杯柠檬水要8美元？
That's driveway robbery.
这简直是敲诈。
- Don't worry, people.
- 别担心，伙计们。
The stack man's got you covered.
堆栈侠会罩着你的。
Lemonade's on me.
柠檬水我请了。
- Yeah! - Whoo!
- 耶！ - 哇！
- That's right.
- 没错。
It may be hot and sunny out,
外面可能又热又晒，
but I'm about to make it rain.
但我马上就要让它下起雨来。
I'm just kidding. That was all fake money.
我开玩笑的。那些都是假钱。
I've got the real stuff in my fur.
我毛里藏的都是真货。
- How are you not sweating?
- 你怎么没流汗？
- Because I had enough money to put fans in here.
- 因为我有足够的钱在这里装风扇。
[fans buzzing]
[风扇嗡嗡作响]
So for our next tournament--
所以，我们的下一个比赛——
- Wait. You want to enter another tournament with us?
- 等等。你想和我们一起参加另一个比赛吗？
- Yup, got to keep it raining.
- 是的，得让钱继续流动。
- But this time, you'll give us
- 但这次，你会给我们平分奖金，对吧？
an even split of the winnings, right?
- 不，得让钱继续流动。
- Nope, got to keep it raining.
- 但我们是一个团队。
- But we're a team.
我们应得我们的一份。
We deserve our fair share.
- 是的，如果不是我们，
- Yeah, and if it wasn't for us,
你还在车库里堆油漆罐。
you'd still be piling paint cans in the garage.
你还在车库里堆油漆罐呢。
- Yeah, but if it wasn't for me,
- 是啊，但如果没有我，
I wouldn't be so rich.
我不会这么有钱。
- How about this?
- 这样如何？
If you don't give us our fair share,
如果你不给我们应得的那份，
we're not gonna be on your team.
我们就不在你队里了。
- Whatever.
- 随便。
I can win that prize money with anybody.
我随便和谁都能赢那笔奖金。
You three are on my team now.
你们三个现在在我队里。
- Cool. I want to make it rain money.
- 酷。我想让钱雨下起来。
- Let's go, new team.
走吧，新团队。
We don't need this.
我们不需要这个。
Let's go find some more expensive lemonade.
去找点更贵的柠檬水吧。
- Go! We don't need you!
走开！我们不需要你！
We totally need him.
我们绝对需要他。
- No, we don't.
不，我们不需要。
We just need to find another stacker
我们只需要找到另一个和他一样厉害的堆叠者。
who's as good as him.
这样我们就能赢，让他脸上洒满金钱。
Then we can win and make it rain in his face.
我加入。
- I'm in. - Let's do it.
我们干吧。
- Where are you going?
你要去哪儿？
What about your hipster lemonade stand?
那你的文艺柠檬水摊怎么办？
- Oh, uh...
哦，呃...
could you guys run it for us while we're gone?
你们能帮我们照看一下摊子吗？
- Sure.
当然可以。
All right, let's do this thing right.
好吧，我们好好干。
♪ ♪
- Hi, my name is Tammy,
嗨，我叫Tammy，
and I'm super excited to try out for Dicky's team.
我超级兴奋能来试试加入Dicky的队伍。
- Oh, Dicky isn't on the team anymore.
哦，Dicky已经不在队里了。
- I'm out.
- 我退出了。
- That is the third person to leave
- 这是第三个因为Dicky不在队里而离开的人。
because Dicky's not on the team.
- 只是为了说清楚，
- Just to be clear,
- Dicky已经不在队里了。
Dicky is no longer on the team.
- 我们该怎么办？
- What are we gonna do?
- 你们会输的。
- You're gonna lose.
- 一，二……
One, two...
- 你在这里做什么？
- What are you doing here?
- 哦，我们只是顺便来看看对手。
- Oh, we just came by to check out the competition.
- 可惜这里没什么对手。
Too bad there isn't any.
太糟糕了，这里什么都没有。
- In your faces.
- 在你们脸上。
- One, two...
- 一，二……
- Dicky! I was just setting that up.
- 迪基！我刚在准备那个。
- Sorry, Dad.
- 对不起，爸爸。
Here's a little something for your troubles.
这是给你们的小小补偿。
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
One...
一……
two, three...
二，三……
- Let me get those cups for you, Mr. Harper.
- 让我帮你拿那些杯子，哈珀先生。
- Thank you very much. I appreciate it.
非常感谢。我很感激。
- It's useless.
这没用。
We will never find somebody
我们永远找不到
who stacks as fast as Dicky.
像Dicky堆得那么快的人。
- I think we just found our new teammate.
我想我们找到了新队友。
- So, Sadie...
那么，Sadie...
I didn't know you were a sport stacker.
我不知道你还是个运动堆叠者。
- Oh, no, I don't stack anymore.
哦，不，我不再堆叠了。
- Oh, why not?
哦，为什么？
- I don't know.
我不知道。
For some reason, all the teams I was on
出于某种原因，我所在的团队
always fell apart.
总是会解散。
- Was that "some reason"
- 那个'某种原因'
that you didn't share your money with your teammates?
- 是因为你没有和队友分享你的钱吗？
- What? No.
- 什么？不是的。
I don't stack for the money.
我不是为了钱而堆叠。
I stack for the love.
我是因为热爱。
- What a coincidence.
- 真巧。
I mean, we stack for the love too.
我是说，我们也是因为热爱。
- Yup, that's us.
- 没错，就是我们。
- All about the love.
- 全都是为了爱。
So since we don't care about the money either,
既然我们也不在乎钱，
would you consider becoming one of the Stackity Doo-Dahs?
你是否考虑过成为Stackity Doo-Dahs的一员？
- Yes!
- 是的！
And I love that name!
而且我喜欢这个名字！
It's spunky and fun.
它既活泼又有趣。
- [pointedly] Thank you, Sadie.
- [意味深长地] 谢谢你，Sadie。
♪ ♪
- Okay, you guys ready to practice?
- 好了，你们准备好练习了吗？
- Absolutely, but just so you know,
- 当然，但你们要知道，
we're not the world's best stackers.
我们不是世界上最好的堆叠高手。
- Guys, don't worry.
伙计们，别担心。
Just do your best.
尽你们最大的努力就好。
- Okay.
好的。
[cups clattering]
（杯子碰撞声）
Stacking is all about the love.
堆叠的关键在于爱。
And there's nothing I love more
而我最喜欢做的事
than turning losers into winners!
就是把失败者变成赢家！
Now stack those up, losers.
现在把它们堆起来，失败者们。
- I'm sorry, Sadie. Are you mad at us?
- 对不起，Sadie。你生我们的气吗？
- Oh, heck, no.
- 哦，天哪，没有。
I'm just embarrassed to be seen in the same room as you, silly.
我只是觉得和你待在同一个房间里很尴尬，傻瓜。
- Will you excuse us for a second?
- 你能让我们离开一会儿吗？
- I'm starting to think the "some reason"
- 我开始觉得Sadie的团队不成功的原因可能是Sadie。
Sadie's teams didn't work out was Sadie.
- 我很抱歉打断你们，
- I'm so sorry to interrupt,
但那些杯子不会自己堆起来的，失败者们。
but those cups aren't gonna stack themselves, losers.
- 你能帮我个忙吗，Sadie，
- Could you do me a favor, Sadie,
别再叫我们失败者了？
and not call us losers?
这很伤人。
It's very hurtful.
- So is my foot halfway up your behind.
我的脚已经半截插在你屁股上了。
Which would you rather have?
你更愿意哪个？
- And we're stacking.
我们在堆杯子。
- Okay.
好吧。
♪ ♪
- Okay, that's enough.
好了，够了。
- Please don't kick us!
请不要踢我们！
- The only thing I'm gonna be kicking
我唯一要踢的
is the other team's patooties,
是对方队伍的屁股，
'cause you guys are winners!
因为你们是赢家！
- Yes! High five.
是的！击掌。
♪♪
♪ ♪
- You guys ready to lose the Get Stacky Invitational?
你们准备好输掉Get Stacky邀请赛了吗？
- You tell me.
你告诉我。
- That's right. We practiced.
没错。我们练习了。
- They were pretty good. Should we have practiced?
他们相当不错。我们应该练习吗？
I mean, I don't even know what cup stacking is.
我的意思是，我甚至不知道什么是叠杯。
- Practice? Practice?
练习？练习？
You're--you're talking about practice.
你在说练习的事。
You've seen me stack,
你见过我堆杯子，
and you're talking about practice?
然后你还在说练习？
Practice?
练习？
I don't need practice.
我不需要练习。
[scoffs] Practice.
[嗤之以鼻] 练习。
[whistle blows]
[哨声响起]
I should have practiced.
我本应该练习的。
- And the winner is--
- 获胜者是--
- The...
- 那个...
Stackity Doo-Dahs!
斯塔克蒂·杜-达兹！
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
呜呼呼呼！
Mommy doesn't love you any less.
妈妈不会因此少爱你一点。
- And now it's time to present the winning team
现在到了颁发获胜团队
with their prize money.
奖金的时刻。
- We did it! We can finally buy our pool!
我们做到了！我们终于可以买我们的泳池了！
- Yes! - Yes!
是的！
- There you are.
- I'd like to announce
在这里。
that we will be donating all of our winnings
我想宣布我们将把所有赢得的奖金
to charity.
给慈善机构。
- [gasps]
- [倒抽一口气]
all: No!
所有人: 不！
- What's wrong? You guys said you weren't in this for the money.
- 怎么了？你们说过不是为了钱。
- We're not.
- 我们不是。
[weakly] Just the love.
[虚弱地] 只是为了爱。
- Good, because the parish
- 那就好，因为教区
is going to buy a new pool with this.
要用这笔钱买个新泳池。
♪♪
♪ ♪
- I can't believe Sadie gave away
- 我不敢相信Sadie把你所有的奖金都给了出去，
all your prize money
在你所有的奖金被Dicky拿走之后。
after Dicky took away all your prize money.
- 但是至少有很多人排队
- But at least a lot of people are in line
买我们的手工柠檬水。
for our artisanal lemonade.
- 是啊，你是怎么做到的？
- Yeah, how'd you do it?
- 简单。我们不再卖你的手工柠檬水了。
- Easy. We stopped selling your artisanal lemonade.
- 然后我们想出了一个新配方：
- And came up with a new recipe:
柠檬、糖、水。- 一美元。
lemon, sugar, water. - One dollar.
- 好吧，谢谢你帮我们看摊子
- Okay, well, thanks for running the stand
在我们离开的时候，但现在我们要接手了。
while we're gone, but we'll take it back now.
在我们离开期间，谢谢你们帮忙看摊，但现在我们要收回去了。
- Sounds good.
听起来不错。
We'll just take all the money we made while we ran it.
我们会拿走我们经营期间赚的所有钱。
- What? No.
什么？不行。
- We did all the work, so we get all the money.
我们做了所有的工作，所以我们应该拿走所有的钱。
All yours.
都是你们的。
- Oh, no. The hipsters are back.
哦，不。那些潮人回来了。
- Maybe you two
也许你们两个
could open your own stand at Mae's house.
可以在Mae家开自己的摊位。
- Hear that, everybody?
听到了吗，大家？
Mae and Miles are opening their own stand.
梅和迈尔斯要开自己的摊位了。
- Yeah! - Sweet.
- 耶！ - 太好了。
- Sorry.
- 对不起。
- Got to give the customers what they want.
- 得满足顾客的需求。
- How does this keep happening to us?
- 这怎么总发生在我们身上？
- We are never going to get that pool.
- 我们永远也买不起那个游泳池了。
- Can I get a cup of lemonade?
- 我能来杯柠檬水吗？
- Uh, sure.
- 呃，当然。
That'll be...
这将是...
one dollar.
一美元。
- Actually, I'm out of cash.
- 实际上，我没钱了。
- Dude, why are you sweating so much?
- 伙计，你怎么出这么多汗？
- My batteries died.
- 我的电池没电了。
- I got an idea.
- 我有个主意。
You know what might help
你知道什么可能有助于
with your little perspiration problem?
解决你这小出汗问题吗？
- A cup of lemonade?
- 一杯柠檬水？
- No, a nice cool pool.
- 不，一个凉爽的泳池。
- This is what I'm talking about.
- 这就是我想说的。
After all this, and you're still trying
经历了这么多，你还在试图
to trick me into doing what you want.
试图诱使我做你想做的事。
- Trick you? Pshhh!
- 诱你？噗！
Oh, here is the cup of lemonade you wanted.
哦，这是你想要的柠檬水。
And drink this while you think about the pool
边喝这个边想想那个我们没打算诱你去的泳池。
we're not trying to trick you into.
- 你知道吗？我不想要一杯柠檬水。
- You know what? I don't want a cup of lemonade.
事实上，我再也不想看到另一杯了。
In fact, I don't ever want to see another cup again.
它只是让我想起
It just reminds me
你们总是不尊重我。
of how you guys are always disrespecting me.
[汗水晃动声]
[sweat sloshing]
- 哇。
- Wow.
哇。
We really messed up.
我们真的搞砸了。
- I know.
我知道。
Maybe we have been disrespecting him.
也许我们一直都在不尊重他。
- And now we've broken him.
而现在我们把他弄崩溃了。
- No, Mae and Miles were right.
不，Mae和Miles是对的。
All you do need is lemon, sugar, and water.
你真正需要的只是柠檬、糖和水。
This is delicious.
这真是美味。
♪ ♪
- [slurps]
（吸溜声）
- Hey, Dicky.
嘿，Dicky。
Why are you drinking from a plate?
你为什么用盘子喝东西？
- I told you I was done with cups.
我告诉过你我不用杯子了。
[slurping]
（吸吮声）
Why are you guys dressed like that?
你们为什么穿成那样？
- Oh, well,
哦，这个，
we're just showing off our new fur coats.
我们只是在展示我们的新皮草外套。
- Pretty sweet, huh?
挺酷的，对吧？
- Is this some kind of joke?
这是某种玩笑吗？
- Nope, we're just respecting your opinion.
不，我们只是尊重你的意见。
- Yeah, you brilliantly suggested
是的，你聪明地建议
we should buy fur coats in the summer
我们应该在夏天买皮草大衣
because we'd get a better deal.
因为那样可以得到更好的价格。
- And we did.
我们确实这么做了。
- You didn't buy those.
你们并没有买那些。
Those are Mom and Dad's old ice-dancing costumes.
那些是爸爸妈妈以前的冰舞服装。
And that's the toilet rug from our bathroom.
还有那是我们浴室的马桶垫。
And by the way, sometimes I miss.
顺便说一句，有时候我会失误。
- Oh, I knew it was you.
哦，我就知道是你。
- I know what you guys are trying to do.
我知道你们在打什么主意。
You're trying to get me back on your team
你们想让我重新加入你们的团队
so you can use me to get your pool.
这样你们就可以利用我去得到你们的泳池。
- No, this isn't about the pool.
不，这跟泳池无关。
This is about you.
这是关于你的。
- It is?
是吗？
- Look what we did to you.
看看我们对你的所作所为。
We made you hate cups so much,
我们让你如此讨厌杯子，
you became a plate slurper.
以至于你变成了一个盘子吸吮者。
- [slurping]
[吸吮声]
Go on.
继续。
- And we're sorry.
- 我们很抱歉。
The truth is, we don't listen to you.
事实上，我们没有听你的。
But we should.
但我们应该这样做。
- You deserve our respect.
- 你值得我们的尊重。
- I do.
- 我确实值得。
[slurping]
[吸吮声]
- And from now on, we're going to listen to you.
- 从现在开始，我们会听你的。
- [slurping]
- [吸吮声]
- But you got to stop that!
- 但你得停止那样做！
- So you're really gonna listen to me?
- 所以你真的会听我的？
Like, if I want to call it "greatfruit,"
比如，如果我想把它叫做“大果子”，
you won't correct me?
你们不会纠正我吧？
- No. - Call it whatever you want.
- 不会。 - 你想叫什么就叫什么。
- Uh...
- 呃...
sure.
当然。
- Wow, you guys really do care about me.
- 哇，你们真的在乎我。
- Of course we do. - Thanks.
- 当然在乎。 - 谢谢。
And since I was kind of a jerk there for a while,
而且，因为我之前有点混蛋，
I owe you guys something.
我欠你们点什么。
How about we go get that pool?
我们去玩那个游泳池怎么样？
- Oh, no, no more competitions.
哦，不，不再有比赛了。
- That's how this whole thing started.
这就是这一切开始的原因。
- Yeah, and you're more important to us
是的，而且你对我们来说比任何游泳池都重要。
than any pool.
实际上，我心里还有另一个主意。
- Actually, I had another idea in mind.
哇！孩子们，我真的很惊讶。
- Wow! Kids, I am impressed.
你们真的把这个柠檬水摊子扭转了。
You really turned this lemonade stand around.
你们的秘诀是什么？
What's your secret?
嗯，我们在我们的配方中加入了一种特色成分。
- Well, we added a signature ingredient
现在就是柠檬、糖、水……
to our recipe.
还有一场表演。
- Now it's lemons, sugar, water...
- 现在我们有柠檬、糖、水...
- And a show.
- 还有一场表演。
[applause]
[掌声]
- Make it rain, Rickity Doo-Dah.
- 让雨下起来，Rickity Doo-Dah。
- Hey, where are all my good pitchers?
- 嘿，我那些好用的投手都去哪儿了？
- Uh...
- 呃...
No idea, Mom.
- 不知道，妈妈。
[laughs nervously]
[紧张地笑]
- Where is she?
- 她在哪儿？
- I'm right behind you.
- 我就在你后面。
And I know where they are.
而且我知道他们在哪里。
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪